

MAGGIE NAN

UX DESIGNER + DEVELOPER

ABOUT

My name is Zhe Nan, and you're welcome to call me Maggie:)

During the past 15 months, I have been working as a web/front-end developer, and gained strong problem solving & analytical thinking skills, which are extremely important for a successful user experience designer.

Three years ago, my passion for user experience paved my way from Electronics Engineering to Information Science; now, I want to take a step further and make it my lifelong career.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2015.11 ~2016.07 YELP San Francisco, CA

UX Driven Web Developer

- Implemented a DE Header Experiment with JavaScript, CSS & Python, built cohorts of dropdown menus in nav bar & created metrics in Google Analytics for A/B testing
- Improving UX culture at Yelp as a core member of the usability group, hosting weekly office hour, and in charge of UsabilityHub experiments & persona interviews

2015.03 ~2015.10

INTERSYSTEMS Cambridge, MA

Front-end Developer

- Created the Twitter Bootstrap plugin from scratch for Zen Mojo with Caché ObjectScript and JavaScript
- Implemented a calendar web application on top of InterSystems Caché database, using Node.js and its Express framework

2014.06 ~2014.08

BIO-RAD Hercules, CA

UX Design Intern

- Redesigned product webpage of T100™ Thermal Cycler to redefine its online shopping experience for customers
- Conducted contextual inquiry using competitive usability evaluations and 30 interviews with stakeholders & customers
- Created Customer Journey Mapping, Behavior Variables and Persona Design to interpret interview results
- Designed low-fi prototype with Balsamiq to meet needs of personas, improved it iteratively with Usability Testings, and turned it into a hi-fi prototype using Axure

607.229.0345 zn45@cornell.edu www.maggienan.com 1 St Francis Pl, San Francisco, CA 94107

EDUCATION

2013.08 Master of Information Science ~2015.01 Cornell University Ithaca, NY

- Focus: Human-Computer

- Interaction
- **GPA**: 3.81
- **Major GPA**: 3.88
- Coursework: HCI Design, Advanced HCI, Software Engineering, Digital Graphics, Oral Communication, Leadership Theory & Practice, Marketing Management

2009.09

Bachelor of Engineering

~2013.06 Sichuan University Chengdu,CN

- Major: Electronic Engineering
- GPA: 3.89, Graduated Magna Cum Laude
- Coursework: Data Structure & Algorithmic Analysis, Operating System, Programming JavaScript, Object-oriented Program Design

SKILLS

Contextual Inquiry	80%
Design Modeling	84%
Storyboarding	70%
Persona Design	86%
Prototyping	84%
Usability Testing	90%
Project Management	83%
Photoshop, Illustrator	79%
HTML, CSS, JavaScript	95%
jQuery	85%
Python	84%
MySQL	80%